batterycare.net 2019-03-20

# BatteryCare - Privacy Policy

### What is BatteryCare?

BatteryCare is a website that provides useful information about how to maintain your laptop battery and also publicly makes available a free software to help you with that task.  
The information on this website and the software available for download are distributed without any cost, however, there are some monetization tools we might use in order provide additional revenue to help cover the projects costs. So, the website and/or the software might be considered “Freeware – Ad supported” and we may use [ third-party advertising companies](http://d21xst4843r7e1.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

### Cookies and site metrics

BatteryCare website does not collect any cookies directly, other than the ones potentially used by Google Adsense advertising embeded in the website and also the and Google Analytics website metric tool.  
We use Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.

### Wrap up

To sum up, BatteryCare does not collect or hold any personal information which can make you identifiable. Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 7th, 2018

batterycaresoftware[at]gmail[dot]com
